{
    "id": "1f16ff3b1cc4472b998965c6283489bd",
    "title": "TOEFL grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c09ffc1d9854465fa07ffbecf4b9466e",
            "title": "TOEFL Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are you going to ………………….. with him when you are in town?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get in touch",
                        "getting touch",
                        "get to touch",
                        "have touch"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ………………….. with cold when she got home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "green",
                        "red",
                        "pink",
                        "blue"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is Martha ...................... the phone.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Before implementing your plans, we need to ………………….. them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "discuss about",
                        "discuss over",
                        "discuss into",
                        "discuss"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which flight is she traveling .....................?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .....................… him since",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "knew",
                        "have known",
                        "had known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Water ..................... at 100 Celsius.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is boiling",
                        "boils",
                        "would boil",
                        "has boiled"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julius Caesar is one of the early …………………. of Shakespeare.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "play",
                        "plays",
                        "drama",
                        "dramas"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Those plates belong ....................... the top shelf.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I prefer stitching clothes for my children ..................... them in the shops.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather buying",
                        "rather than to buy",
                        "rather than buying",
                        "to buy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}